http://www.pro-linear.com/privacy

Product Training
Industry News (Vault)
Contact
Privacy PolicyGeneralThis Privacy Statement applies to Staub Electronics Ltd., (hereinafter referred to as "Staub", "we", "us" or "our" in this Privacy Statement) in the course of our business in Canada. This Privacy Statement is designed to tell individuals with whom we may interact in the course of our business in Canada as well as other who purchase our products about our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, including information you provide over the telephone, by mail or facsimile and via our Web Sites. Staub maintains www.staub.ca, www.staubcommercial.ca, www.purposeav.ca, www.connectedhomes.ca, www.staubtraining.ca and admin.staub.ca (the "Web Sites"). This Privacy Statement does not apply to personal information about our employees or information that is not personal information.What personal information will Staub collect?Staub collects personal information from you that you provide to us voluntarily. Such personal information may include personal contact information, such as name, address, and telephone number; your personally identifiable comments/questions about our products and services and information required to order our products and services (including credit card information.)Staub collects personal information about its guests and visitors. Specifically, visitors to Staub's offices may be asked to provide their name, telephone number, and organization name. Staub collects this personal information for premises security and disaster preparedness purposes. Staub may also install video cameras in certain areas on its premises and will post signs notifying individuals of the existence and purpose of any such cameras.In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personal information. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our Web Sites. If that material is not linked to other information that is "personal information" about you, the non-personal information is not subject to this Privacy Policy.If we obtain personal information from third parties, for example to send promotional mailings, we seek assurances that the provider has received consent to provide that information to us.In addition, please remember that any personal information that is voluntarily posted to any public area of the Web Sites - such as a chat room -- may always be accessible to other visitors and that there is nothing Staub can do to prevent collection, use or disclosure of this information by those visitors.If you apply for a position at Staub, we will collect the personal information contained in, and generated in relation to, your application, in order to evaluate your application and assess whether to offer you a position at Staub. For candidates who are not offered or do not accept a position, we normally retain this information for a reasonable time, in the event that an appropriate position becomes available or that you re-apply to Staub, unless you ask us not to retain this information and there is no legal requirement that we retain it. If you accept a position at Staub, the information will be retained in accordance with our privacy procedures applicable to the personal information of employees of Staub.In relation to potential employees, in addition to personal information that you provide, we may collect personal information from:The third parties you provide as references in support of your application; andIndividuals involved in the evaluation and review process.How will Staub use and disclose the personal information we collect?We use and disclose this personal information for the following purposes:To fulfill your orders, to process your credit card payments and to collect amounts you owe;To assess your eligibility for credit that you may have requested from us;To respond to your requests for information and service and to communicate with you;To carry out internal financial processes including to credit our sales representatives;For internal research to better understand your needs and ways in which we can improve our products, services and Web Sites;To manage and administer our business;To send product information and special offers, including sample texts sent to educators, that we think may be of interest to you; in support of joint marketing and promotion activities with related entities, and to permit those related entities to send information or offers regarding their products and services to you, in each case if you have provided your consent to receiving such materials;As permitted or required by law; to enforce our Terms of Use and Terms of Sale and other agreements; and for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.We may also use or disclose your personal information for other purposes, which we will disclose at the time of collection.We sometimes transfer personal information to others, including to affiliated entities or unrelated companies, that carry out certain functions on our behalf such as order fulfillment and data processing. In those cases we require those entities not to use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than as directed by Staub.Your personal information may be used by Staub and shared with others connected with the contemplated or actual financing, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of Staub's business or assets, including for the purposes of permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed with such transaction or business relationship, or to fulfill any disclosure obligations we have to such parties. If we do sell or assign all or part of our business, the purchaser or assignee will be able to use and disclose personal information to the same extent, under the same conditions and for substantially the same purposes as Staub, as described in this Privacy Statement.General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)We are a Data Controller of your information.Staub's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:Staub needs to perform a contract with youYou have given Staub permission to do soProcessing your personal information is in Staub's legitimate interestsStaub needs to comply with the lawStaub will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us using one of the methods at the end of this Privacy Policy.In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on youThe right of rectificationThe right to objectThe right of restrictionThe right to data portabilityThe right to withdraw consentLog Files: Staub follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this as a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.Cookies and Web Beacons: Like any other website, Staub uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.Your ConsentYour consent to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information may be given in various ways. Consent can be express (express consent may be oral, in writing or electronic), implied (such as when you provide your name and address in order for us to send you products you have ordered or information you have requested) and in some jurisdictions may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian or a person having a power of attorney). Generally, if you provide us with your personal information, we will assume that you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such information as described in this Privacy Statement, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection.Collection, Use or Disclosure Without Your ConsentIn certain limited circumstances our collection, use or disclosure of your personal information without consent is permitted or required by law, for example, to collect a debt you owe to us or to comply with a subpoena or court order.What if I do not want my personal information collected, used or disclosed?If you do not want your personal information collected, used or disclosed by us, please do one of the following: 1) follow the procedures, where available, indicated at the point of collection such as to "opt out" from the particular purposes of use and disclosure, or 2) if no "opt out" is available, do not submit personal information to us if you do not want us to collect, use or disclose it. If you have submitted personal information and later wish to withdraw your consent to its retention, use or disclosure, please contact us as indicated below. You may withdraw your consent, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice.Please understand, that without your consent, we may not be able to provide certain goods or services to you. For example, if you do not provide consent to collect and use personal information necessary to process an order that you wish to place, or if you withdraw your consent to uses that are necessary to fulfill your request, we may not be able to process your order or to supply those products to you. We will endeavour to advise you if this should happen.SecurityWe will protect your personal information using physical, electronic or managerial procedures designed to protect the integrity, security and appropriate use of your personal information and to prevent theft, loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. Authorized employees, agents and mandataries of Staub who require the personal information will be permitted to access personal information, to fulfill the purpose for which the information was collected and the purposes disclosed in the section above entitled "How will Staub use and disclose the personal information we collect?". We will retain your personal information as is required for these purposes, subject to reasonable legal limitation periods and statutory or regulatory retention requirements and our document retention policies.Although we have enacted security measures for our Web Sites, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of our Web Sites or the security of information that you submit (or that we send to you) over the Internet, since no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. Your use of the Internet and electronic mail is at your own risk. You should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail or posting on the Staub Web Sites.Our Links to Other Web SitesThe Staub Web Sites may contain links or references to other web sites to which this Privacy Statement does not apply. Staub is not responsible for the data collection and use practices of companies or organizations to which the Staub Web Sites may provide links. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every web site you visit.What information may be stored on your computer?You may browse our Web Sites anonymously as long as you do not register or buy products on-line. We do not store information on your computer in the form of "cookies" or similar files when you simply browse our Web Site. When you register on the site, purchase products or otherwise when you are aware and agree, Staub does use cookies to facilitate your registration profile or purchase. "Cookies" are small files containing information that a web site creates when someone visits the site. Generally users' browsers can be set to reject cookies or to notify you when receiving a cookie. Some web site features may not be available if your browser is not set to accept cookies.Special Notice To ParentsWe have no intention of seeking personal information about minors who visit our Web Sites. If such information is collected, the same privacy policies will apply to that information. In addition, if we can identify a user as a minor, the personal information will not be used for further marketing and promotion unless the minor's guardian has consented. We encourage you to ask your children to seek your permission before providing information about themselves or their family over the Internet.Special Notice To ChildrenAsk your parent or guardian for permission before you send any personal information over the Internet, including to our Web Sites.How to Contact Us - Access to InformationStaub may establish and maintain a file of your personal information at our offices for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement. To request access to, or correction of, your personal information, please write to Staub's Privacy Compliance Officer at Staub Electronics Ltd, #160 - 11791 Hammersmith Way, Richmond, BC, V7A 5C6. In some circumstances Staub may not be able to provide access to your information or to all of it. For example, Staub will not provide access to information if doing so would reveal personal information about a third party, would reveal confidential commercial information, or if it is protected by solicitor-client privilege or was generated in the course of a formal dispute resolution process. If you have any questions, or if you wish to make inquiries, express concerns or make a complaint about our personal information practices, you may (1) write to the Privacy Compliance Officer at the above address, (2) call the Privacy Compliance Officer at our toll free number 1-888-470-2211 (3) send us an email at kEncEmailqsjwbdzAtubvc/db; or (4) fax us at 1-888-844-7316. A letter, fax, or email is the most reliable way to convey your concerns or wishes.Updates to this Privacy StatementWe reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Statement. If this Privacy Statement materially changes, we will take reasonable measures to notify you of these changes, including posting a copy of the revised Privacy Statement on our Web Sites. Your continued consent to our collection, use and disclosure practices following notification of any material change and/or your continued access to the Web Sites following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Statement shall constitute your acceptance of those changes. You may also contact us if you would like us to send you a copy of the most current version of this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement was last revised March 2017.
